in 2019 I had to save 30 000 from
working at Dunkin Donuts and money that
I ended up borrowing from my family and
I lost everything in just a matter of
three months trading Forex and even with
that I entered major depression I messed
up the relationship with my family and
I've actually never told the story
before so this is how I went
it all started when in 2018 I was a
simple Dunkin Donuts worker where I was
making eight dollars and fifty cents an
hour I was earning anywhere from fifteen
hundred dollars every single month and
this is where I was putting in eight
hour days 40 hour weeks and I was still
extremely unhappy and I truly didn't
want to know what I wanted to do with my
life and I remember extremely clear how
one day at the beginning of 2019 I
decided to turn my life around
completely and this is all because of
one simple thing I got a red light
traffic ticket that completely changed
my life forever that ticket changed the
way of me looking at money and time
forever because that ticket was
158 and precisely that week I didn't
work half of the week where my paycheck
was a hundred and fifty eight dollars at
the end of the week so literally the
whole entire week that I put in to work
at Dunkin Donuts went straight to just
pay off this red light ticket and this
ticket had me rethinking my whole entire
life and at that very moment that
completely changed my way of thinking
because what I was doing was wasting a
week of my life of working just to pay
off a red light ticket that I actually
got rushing to get to work so I didn't
get fired I didn't find this fair at all
this is where I made a decision and I
decided to no longer value my time at
eight dollars and fifty cents an hour
because clearly it's not enough to
barely make ends meet and this is where
I decided to start figuring out how can
I make the money work for me and not me
work for the money and this is
accompanied by the action that I took to
figure out how can I make money online
and I'm sure you guys have all been
there like we all see these
multi-millionaire gurus and ads and we
all think they're a scam personally
myself included but what I didn't
realize is that they're in a much better
position than I was so I'm like you know
what why not give it a shot so by that
time I had discovered four different
choices first one being trading stocks I
decided to try it out but it only took
me about two weeks to stop it because I
needed a minimum of 25 000 art and it
was extremely complex and I didn't want
to put all of my life savings along with
my family's money into something that
the majority of the people say you're
going to lose right off the bat so it
was very very high risk very complicated
and I saw a little reward and potential
in it then I realized that there was
Amazon Drop Shipping and this one caught
my attention really quick because a
buddy of mine he had actually been doing
it for six months ahead of me so he was
already been doing Amazon for six months
but I got very very uninterested because
he was doing it for six months and had
no results so I almost saw it as a waste
of time if I would have attempted to do
it with him and next I decided to
venture into the world of Airbnb
property management and I actually ended
up taking a couple of courses here
because I was really looking up to Grant
Cardone at the time and he did an
interview with Brian page where he was
doing short-term rental property
Arbitrage and this really caught my
attention so I took the courses I
learned I applied the strategies but I
had no results because the laws here in
Miami for short-term rentals they were
very complex I never really get the
licenses it just took too much time
along with a lot of capital to back up
the leases that you had to sign in order
to get these properties and it went much
deeper than I ever expected it would be
and then that's where I found trading
forks and I decided to stay in this
Niche because the entry barrier was by
far the lowest than any of the others
that I had just mentioned and the risk
to reward was by far the largest all you
realistically need is a laptop 100 bucks
to get started and some Wi-Fi so you can
mark with your charts and the margins
are a hundred percent so whatever you
make on your trades you keep a hundred
percent of it obviously other than taxes
depending where you're living there you
pay your taxes on your own but other
than that the margins are a hundred
percent on what you make on your trades
but what really caught my attention is
that you can day trade within Forex
meaning you can make money 24.5 so
there's opportunities to make money all
day all night unlike the stock market
that's open from nine to five the Forex
Market is open 24 5 so there's endless
opportunity so as I'm getting deeper and
deeper into this Niche I realize that
you can turn a hundred dollars into a
thousand X extremely fast because you
can use leverage to maximize your
trading profits and this led me to build
a brand new mentality I was no longer
scared of the money and I started to
learn ways how to use it as a tool to
make me more money and I started to feel
more and more confident that I could
actually make a living trading Forex
regardless of what everybody said or
people calling it a scam or even more my
family members not believing in me and
this is where I became more and more
obsessed with trading forms
I was studying 10 hour days weekends and
everything for a period of five to six
months this is where I called my dark
mode my only priority was to focus as
much as I can about these financial
markets know everything about the
business all of the ins and all of the
outs and soon after I began to
understand the actual flow of how the
markets work I was envisioning myself
driving through my new Lambo down my
neighborhood showing my family members
and telling all the people I didn't
believe me I told you so because since I
put so much time into this I started
seeing the patterns again and again and
again so just a matter of time until I
capitalized off the next pattern
and all of this led me to getting my
first result at first obviously the
results weren't the best however I was
visualizing myself how I was going to
able to make a living from trading for
it I started to turn into a new person a
much stronger person a much smarter
person I started getting comfortable
with being uncomfortable in the markets
because there's no room for messing
around when it comes to trading in these
markets
[Music]
and as time went by I started to learn
from my mistakes and I would catch
myself from doing something wrong which
would have cost me thousands of dollars
and having more and more acceptable
results I still wasn't earning much
money but I wasn't losing it as much as
I was in the beginning and little by
little I was understanding the Arts of
trading more and more I was
understanding how the market moved based
off of trending markets and more
importantly how crucial the psychology
role factors into trading and with good
time thanks to very strict discipline I
started to have more and more positive
results and he was already earning money
it wasn't much but it was already
profitable I was already generating an
extra five thousand dollars a month in
just the first year and here's where I
reached a great Epiphany and it was when
I really realized what allowed me to
take the first sleep or as I call it the
aha moment
[Music]
this is when I realized that the only
thing that I had to do was to put a
hundred percent of my focus on only
taking the best quality Trace setup and
not focus on trying to get on every
single trade focus on quality over
quantity and by thinking and acting this
way things in my trading has started to
change forever and this led me to think
that everything from this moment on
everything was going to be golden and
perfect and that's what I answered what
I thought was my Golden Arrow at this
very moment my life had changed
completely
[Music]
when you stopped being a problem and I
started buying new things for myself
like I think everybody would I bought my
first Rolex for seven thousand dollars I
bought a brand new Mercedes S550 because
I wanted to feel like a big boss you
know driving around in Miami and my
bands with my brand new Rolex and here I
started to relax enjoy life because I
had never really been able to buy nice
things and have certain Liberties but at
that time in my life I was able to have
and even though I started to experience
all of this sudden and success or this
luxury lifestyle it all came with a very
big lesson
[Music]
hidden with inside of it by then I had
to manage to achieve eighty thousand
dollars in 60 days and I lost everything
in trading there was something that I
was ignoring and it took a toll on me
that's risk management and at that
moment in my life I wasn't humble enough
to realize that I was making this
mistake am I not changing this Behavior
the worse happened I had lost the last
thirty thousand dollars that I had in
the bank account in the matter of 60
days this is something that I could not
believe that happened and I went into
complete denial and I didn't accept the
reality and in turn this came with great
frustration and Great Depression I
remember how I tried to get out of the
hole without success by trying to flip
small accounts fast and trying to make
my money back and what I didn't really
allow myself to understand was that this
great denial was causing me great
suffering and much much pain that's when
I decided to turn around everything that
was happening I decided to get into dark
mode and begin to analyze in a cold and
calculated away what was thinking me and
not allowing me to move forward little
by little I began to detect the patterns
that led me to this situation I still
realized that only three specific
actions were responsible for causing the
thirty thousand dollars that I lost in
60 days once I identified this error I
took it upon myself to eliminate it
completely and forever what I did was
just focus on the best trade setups and
not focus on taking all the trades the
market has to offer after when the good
trade presents itself use risk
management it is a mandatory rule of
mine from that moment on and for the
rest of my life because not every trade
is guaranteed to be a win and most
importantly let the winning trades run
and cut your losses short thanks to all
this I had reached a new level where I
was no longer making mistakes and all of
this allowed me to live a real true
success
[Music]
yeah
and From This Moment On I acquired a new
philosophy known as set and forget and
all of this came with it new results on
a money level on a personal level
relationship friendships and as soon as
I started to realize the same applied to
all the areas of my life that's when the
new big big results started to come in I
started to earn numbers like these these
these and even like these I started to
reach new levels and reach new records
like my first million in which I managed
to achieve it in just under one year
without having to go through any more of
my losing streaks in my trading at all
completely stopped it would allow me to
get to where I am today was trading for
it my journey was very long and a very
painful one but I'm very convinced that
it doesn't have to be like that for
everyone that's exactly why I have a
recorded video on how to successfully
get into this business so you do not
make the same mistakes that I do and you
get results just like me you can watch
it down below appreciate you guys
watching the video all the way to the
end make sure to like comment and
subscribe and I'll see you guys in the
next